# Wussu Ifeoluwa

Content Manager

A serious-minded Crypto and Web3 content writer who is proficient in creating engaging content that attracts and converts potential clients, collectors, and users. With more than 3 years of experience and skin in the game, I have developed and, with the aid of my writing skills, assisted numerous entities in the crypto sector in expanding and achieving their goals.

## **CONTACT ME**

- Lagos, Nigeria
- ifeoluwadaniel01@gmail.com
- ☐ https://linktr.ee/en\_zoe
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/i feoluwa-wussu-ba2274180/

## **EDUCATION**

Physics Electronics University/College Details 2013 - 2018

Wordpress Website mastery Udemy 2017

Token Engineering
Token Engineering Academy
Ongoing

## **SKILLS**

Written Communication

**Content Marketing** 

Search Engine Optimization

Social Media Marketing

Blockchain Analysis

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Content Manager

Jun 2022 - Present

#### **IncubateX**

- Wrote the company's whitepaper.
- Wrote an E-book that converted over 100 potential collectors to the company.
- Charged with writing and publishing all forms of educative and marketing pieces.
- Manage a team of marketers (shillers) to target prospects and bring them in.
- Curated and managed the entire content strategy across all platforms (blog, social, articles etc.)

#### Content Manager

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

#### WePlay Labs

- Curated 3-4 strategic contents weekly which maintained the company's tone.
- Curated interesting content that organically increased the company's Twitter & Medium following from fewer than 20 to well over 3600.
- Assisted with other marketing efforts and wrote pieces for advertisement, newsletter, and marketing campaigns (AMAs, Airdrops).
- Edited the whitepaper, company's website, blogs, and webinars.

#### **Content Writer**

Feb 2022 - May 2022

### WhalesHeaven

- Researched relevant trends in the Crypto and Defi space and pitch new content ideas.
- Created 4 engaging articles each week based on the current company's products.
- Conducted simple keyword research & use SEO guidelines to rank on Google's 1st page.
- Participated in the brainstorming of new ideas for campaign activation activities like Airdrops and Meme contests.

## Content Writer

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022

#### Secretum

- Ensured that all written copy adhered to the brand's tone and met the highest editorial standards.
- Teamed up with marketing and graphic designers to create content for the company's social media accounts.
- Informed and educated prospects and members about the project's utility and updates during weekly Twitter spaces and AMAs.

## **REFERENCES**

# **Available On Request**